export const healthcareSolutions = [
    {
        question: "Patient Management Apps",
        answer: "Streamline clinical workflows with our EMR/EHR systems designed for the seamless capture and storage of patient data. Our healthcare software development company ensures these systems are intuitive, interoperable, and fully compliant with healthcare standards."
    },
    {
        question: "Appointment Scheduling",
        answer: "Answer 2"
    },
    {
        question: "Telemedicine Solutions...",
        answer: "Answer 3"
    },
    {
        question: "E-prescriptions...",
        answer: "Answer 4"
    },
    {
        question: "Health Monitoring Apps...",
        answer: "Answer 5"
    },
    {
        question: "Secure Messaging",
        answer: "Answer 6"
    },
]

export const realEstateSolutions = [
    {
        question: "Online Booking Platforms for Properties",
        answer: "Streamline clinical workflows with our EMR/EHR systems designed for the seamless capture and storage of patient data. Our healthcare software development company ensures these systems are intuitive, interoperable, and fully compliant with healthcare standards."
    },
    {
        question: "Centralized Property Listing Systems",
        answer: "Answer 2"
    },
    {
        question: "Property Management Systems",
        answer: "Answer 3"
    },
    {
        question: "Apartment rental apps",
        answer: "Answer 4"
    },
    {
        question: "Home Search and Discovery Tools",
        answer: "Answer 5"
    },
    {
        question: "Land Rental Management Apps",
        answer: "Answer 6"
    },
    {
        question: "Brokerage Management Solutions",
        answer: "Answer 7"
    },
    {
        question: "Lead Tracking & management Tools",
        answer: "Answer 8"
    }
]